bollywoodbuzz.in 2009-12-23

# Fair Use Guide/Privacy Policy | Bollywood Buzz

**Want to Link, Quote or Reprint?**

If you are interested in linking, quoting, or reprinting articles from Bollywood Buzz in whole or in part, please do read our copyright policy:

**# If you want to link from your site to Bollywood Buzz**

You are welcome to use short quotes from Bollywood Buzz in your website or blog as long as proper credit is given. But please quote only short excerpts – up to one paragraph – from our site when you make the link.

**# You must credit Bollywood Buzz when you quote**

Always provide a hyperlink (full URL) to the article where the quote is from. Don’t hyperlink just to the homepage. Copy quoted material exactly, enclose it in quotations marks, and mention Bollywood Buzz immediately before or after the quote.

**Privacy Policy**

The privacy of our visitors to Bollywood Buzz is important to us. At Bollywood Buzz, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important.

Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit Bollywood Buzz, and how we safeguard your information.  We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**# Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.  The information in the log files include your IP (Internet Protocol) address, your ISP (Internet Service Provider), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**# Cookies and Web Beacons**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site.  This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on Bollywood Buzz to support our site.  Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.  This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (for example, showing New Delhi real estate ads to someone in New Delhi) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

**# DoubleClick DART cookies**

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements).  This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (“interest based targeting”).  The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Goa, you may see Goa hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about cricket).  DART uses “non personally identifiable information”.  It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers.  You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.  However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.  This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program.  Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

**# Newsletter**

If a visitor wishes to subscribe to our newsletter (powered by Feedblitz), we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our visitors’ privacy, we provide a way to opt-out of these communications.

**# Contact Information**

If visitors have any questions, suggestions or advertising offers regarding our site, please contact us.
